Devanshi Goel

Computer Science Undergraduate

A full stack web developer,technical blogger,machine learning enthusiast and a programmer striving to apply my skills to solve some real life issues.Loves collaborating with communities and working in teams. I like mentoring peeps and helping them learn the skills I know.Practical experience in management gained through several university projects.##Lets_Learn&Grow_Together



devanshi0608@gmail.com

8384863399

bareilly, India 👂

devanshi-123.github.io/portfolio/

linkedin.com/in/devanshi-goel-81b252195 in

github.com/Devanshi-123 🌎

medium.com/@devanshi0608 N

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Computer Science Engineering

National Institute Of Technology Patna.

08/2018 - Present

Current C.GP.A: 9.51

Major Courses covered:

 Data Structure and Algorithm , Operating System , Web Development

Extra Curricular Activities:

A stage performer, a debater, blogger, member of music club

Achievements:

- Won the title of miss melange for stage performance in techno cultural fest nit patna
- Came first in the handball game during intramurals.
- Our team made up to finals in parliamentary debate

Experience

Full Stack Web Development Intern at Statekind

06/2020 - 08/2020

Software engineering virtual experienceJp Morgan Chase&CO

08/2020 - 08/2020

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- 1. Poshan Abhiyan (12/2019 Present)
- A website aiming to provide help to the anganwadi workers.
- This was a team project me and my team of 5 members made this.
- Tech stack : html,css,mongodb,nodejs
- 2. https://goel-weather-forecast.herokuapp.com/ (08/2019 - Present) ♂
- A weather forecasting website based on users location and can also predict possiblity of rain
- Tech stack-html,css,javascript
- 3.Search Companion App (06/2020 Present)
- A web app which can make your search journey very easy by searching recipes ,images and different stuff
- Tech stack-Reactjs Redux Reactrouter

Machine learning projects ♂

- 1 Mood music (A ml model to predict mood of a person based on song and recommend more songs depending on mood.
- 2 Stock Market Prediction (Using different ensemble learning and deep learning methods)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML & CSS	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Reactjs	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
C++	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Data Structure and Algorithm	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ
Nodejs and Mongodb	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ
Machine Learning	\bullet \bullet \circ \circ
Python	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

ORGANIZATIONS

Student Coordinator Alumni Cell Nit Patna (01/2020 - Present)

Works to keep our alumni connected to their college and help the college peeps

Coding Team Lead Hackslash Club NIT Patna (08/2020 - Present)

Organise activities to help students learn data structures algorithms and competitive programming

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador (08/2020 - Present)

To collaborate with people all around the world ,learn new technologies and implement to solve real world issues

Web Departmental Lead at Google Developer Student Club Nit Patna (09/2020 - Present)

To come up with web solution for different social problems.

Technical Content writer at Medium (06/2020 - Present)

Write different blogs to help students learn some concepts

CERTIFICATES

DataCamp Certificates for various courses on python and machine learning (06/2020 - Present)

Machine Learning Deep Learning Show (06/2020 - Present)

Alpha Student Ambassador Certificate (09/2020 - Present)

Certificate of completion for c and java by eschool (07/2019 - Present)

Certificate for runner up ntpc debate (11/2019 - Present)